<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="12"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[h School. Reimagined.]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[roducing
Bard Academy
at Simon’s Rock,
the nation’s first
two-year high school
for boarding and
day students.

Opening the fall of 2015.]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[t if …

...there was a school that welcomed your big ideas, your imagination?
That encouraged your curiosity. That didn’t try to limit it or quiet it.
That respected its power, gave it room to breathe and helped you own it,
shape it and develop it in a way that made sense to you.

...your classes were taught by college professors and you loved what you
were learning? And the conversation didn’t have to end when the bell
rang? But continued over lunch with a professor in the dining hall, with
friends in your dorm, or while rock-climbing in a state-of-the art athletic
center?

What if high school only lasted two years? If after completing the 10th
grade, you became a freshman in the nation’s best early college?

It does exist. We are Bard Academy at Simon’s Rock.]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[we are.

Bard Academy at Simon’s Rock is the nation’s only independent school for 9th and 10th
grade boarding and day students where bright, curious and motivated young people like you
pre­pare to enter college two years early.

After completing 10th grade, you’ll begin full time collegiate study at Bard College at
Simon’s Rock, the nation’s only dedicated residential early college. The College offers the
opportunity to earn your Associate of Arts degree in two years and your Bachelor of Arts
degree after two more.

If you love to learn and don’t want to wait for intensive critical inquiry and advanced
academic challenge, Bard Academy at Simon’s Rock may be right for you.

Why high school in two years?

At Bard Academy at Simon’s Rock, we believe the traditional American high school isn’t
for everyone. For too many students, junior and senior year is less about learning and more
about preparing for standardized testing, filling out college applications and taking courses
that look good on a resume.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[believe that two years of concentrated study at the high-school level, as opposed to the
con­ventional four, is the best preparation for college. Modeled after successful day programs
at the Bard High School Early Colleges in New York, Newark, and Cleveland, Bard Academy
provides an enriching high school experience while creating a seamless transition into
college life and work, right when you are most ready for it.

Our vision of a better high school.

Who better to prepare you for college than your future college professors? At Bard Academy,
your courses are taught by Simon’s Rock faculty, who are not only accomp­ lished scholars
and leaders in their fields but also experienced teachers of younger students.

The Academy capitalizes on the intellectual strengths of the College, with semin­ ar-style
classes that facilitate authentic exchange between students; a curriculum that teaches clear
writing as a means to and reflection of clear thinking; and opportunities for interdisci­plinary
inquiry, as well as sustained, independent research.]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[e at the Academy.

At Bard Academy, you’ll live with people your own age, who want to talk about the things
you want to talk about and do the things you’re interested in.

Our beautiful campus offers Academy students access to acres of fields and trails, plus
the resources and state-of-art facilities of the College. The Daniel Arts Center hosts
internationally re­nowned artists and performers, and the Kilpatrick Athletic Center features
a swimming pool, fitness center, rock climbing wall and various class offerings.

You can walk or take a shuttle to downtown Great Barrington, named “Best Small Town” by
Smithsonian Magazine for its food, art and culture. Or go further and explore the Berkshires,
famous for its ski resorts, hiking trails, museums and shops. Meanwhile,
New York and Boston are less than three hours away, and there are frequent field trips to
each city.]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[t every parent should know.

If your child is looking for a challenging, engaging experience, Bard Academy may be the
right answer.

The Academy shares the College’s philosophy, faculty, and facilities. Students will reside in
a separate dormitory with a dedicated resi­dential staff and study their own liberal arts and
sciences curriculum. Each student will be assigned a faculty advisor, and students in the
College will serve as academic tutors and mentors.

Visit us today.

See firsthand what a unique educational experience might be in store for your child. To
schedule an appointment, call 800.235.7186 or email
bardacademy@simons-rock.edu.]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[D ACADEMY AT SIMON’S ROCK                                                        NON-PROFIT ORG
84 ALFORD ROAD                                                                     U.S. POSTAGE PAID
GREAT BARRINGTON, MA 01230-1978
bardacademy@simons-rock.edu                                                          PERMIT NO. 36
800.235.7186                                                                         PITTSFIELD, MA

                                                                                           01201

                                 092014TR]]></page></pages></Search>